freemp3.us.com 2009-02-02

# Free mp3 Website » TOS/Privacy Policy

| | Looking for a certain artist, song, or mp3 player device? FreeMp3.us.com is committed to helping you enjoy a positive web experience. We hope our page on **TOS/Privacy Policy** is useful to you. If you have any questions or comments about the article file, please tell us.

If you are having trouble with a broken source link, please contact us so that we can update the link.  
  
---|---|---  
  
**Privacy Policy for www.freemp3.us.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at freemp3@quadium32.com.

At www.freemp3.us.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.freemp3.us.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.freemp3.us.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.freemp3.us.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, .

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.freemp3.us.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.freemp3.us.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.freemp3.us.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Advertisements

| | Still haven't found what you are looking for? Thanks for visiting freemp3.us.com, your #1 source for information on legal free mp3 downloads. Again, if any of our mp3/source links are broken, please let us know so we can update the link. You can contact us through information on the TOS/Privacy Policy page. We will try to get an active link to your mp3 information working again as soon as possible. However, we try to avoid ever having broken legal mp3 information links on our site, so hopefully all mp3 source links will work for you.   
A note to our visitors: please only download legal mp3 files. This way you will be supporting the music artists whom you love. We only post legal mp3 links on our website, so you don't need to worry here.   
---|---|---
